Finding aid to the Undergraduate Life records CA.MS.01013
Smith College Archives
Undergraduate Life records
1875-1999
Smith College Archives
Smith College -- Students
CA.MS.01013
38.042 linear feet (69 containers)
Undergraduate Life records contains papers related to student clothes and fashions, Distinct Groups (informational files on foreign students, minorities, Ada Comstock Scholars), Student Government (includes Council and House minutes, course critiques, SGA records), and Student Publications.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials in the Smith College Archives are open for use, with the following exceptions: "Office Files," files of records created for the use of the administrative unit that created them, are closed to research for a period of 10 years following their creation. Student academic records, student disciplinary records, and all records containing FERPA-covered student information are closed during the lifetime of the student. Student records created 100 years or more ago are assumed to be about deceased students. In all cases, the College Archives will continue to provide public access to materials that were intended to be public at the time of their creation (press releases, publications, etc.)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown.
Scope and Contents
Undergraduate Life records contains papers related to student clothes and fashions (news clippings, photographs); Distinct Groups (informational files on foreign students, minorities, Ada Comstock Scholars, including pamphlets, correspondence, photographs, newsletters, organization); Student Government (includes Council and House minutes, course critiques, SGA records); and Student Publications (complete runs of student newspapers, literary magazines, etc.).
- Special Students, 1894-1925 (Box 1379)
- Clothes, 1875-1960s (Box 3000)
- Distinct Groups (Box 3027)
  Scope and Contents
  This box includes papers on foreign students, geographical groups, and minorities.
- Student Government Association
  - Student Council- General (Box 3090)
  - Student Council- Minutes, 1919-04-1959-09 (Box 3090, Box 3091, Box 3092)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1959-10-1968-02 (Box 2093)
  - House of Representatives- General (Box 3094)
  - House of Representatives- Minutes, Agenda, and Correspondence, 1935-04-1970-04 (Box 3096, Box 3095)
  - House of Representatives- President's Notes for Meetings, 1938-04-1959-03 (Box 3096)
  - General- A-Z, 1919-1972 (Box 3097, Box 3098, Box 3099, Box 3100, Box 3101)
  - Curriculum Committee- General (Box 3102)
  - Curriculum Committee- Course Critiques, 1967-1986
  - Curriculum Committee- Aspects, 1985-1999
  - Community Service Organizations
    - College Relief Committee, 1945-1960 (Box 3107)
    - Service Fund, 1944-1960 (Box 3107, Box 3107.1)
    - Service Organization of Smith College, 1960-1968 (Box 3107.1)
    - Service Organization of Smith (SOS), 1968 (Box 3107.1, Box 3107.2)
    - Charity Ball, 1932-1959 (Box 3108)
    - International Student's Day, 1947 (Box 3108.1)
    - Sophia's Circus, 1941 (Box 3108.1)
- Photographs, 1988 (Box 3109.1, Box 3109.2)
- Student Publications
  - Publications A-G (Box 3110)
  - Publications H-R (Box 3111)
  - Publications S-Z (Box 3111.1)
  - Campus Cat, 1918-1952 (Box 3112)
  - Campus Cat
  - Campus Cat (Box 3111.2)
  - Can We Talk? (Box 3110.1)
  - Current
  - Grecourt Review, 1958-1996 (Box 3112.2)
  - Grecourt Review
  - Green Age Literary Review (Box 3112.1)
  - Labrys (Box 3112.3)
  - Mss. (Box 3115)
  - Mss.
  - Opinion (Box 3117.3)
  - Opinion (Box 3119)
  - Outlook (Box 3115)
  - Outlook
  - New Current
  - Press Board (Box 3116)
  - Press Board (scrapbooks), 1908-1910 (Box 3116.1)
  - Press Board (scrapbooks), 1910-1925 (Box 3116.2)
  - Press Board (scrapbooks), 1910-1924 (Box 3116.3)
  - SCAN
  - SCAN, 1942-1943 (Box 3119.1)
  - SCAN (Box 3119.2)
  - SCAN (Box 3119.3)
  - SCAN (records) (Box 3119)
  - Sequence (Box 3117)
  - Sequence
  - Smith College Monthly (Box 3113)
  - Smith College Monthly
  - Smith College Weekly, 1929-1940 (Box 3120.1)
  - Smith College Weekly (General, index, photographs) (Box 3117.4)
  - Smith College Weekly (unbound copies) (Box 3119)
  - Smith College Weekly (unbound copies) (Box 3119.3)
  - Smith College Weekly (bound copies)
  - Smith College Weekly (records) (Box 3119)
  - Smith College Weekly (humor issues) (Box 3119)
  - Smith College Weekly (Pictorial Sections), 1924-1948 (Box 3120.1)
  - Smith College Weekly and SCAN Index, 1911-1950 (Box 3120)
  - Smith College Weekly and Sophian photographs (Box 3119)
  - Smith Review (Box 3117)
  - Smith Review
  - Sophian
  - Sophian (general) (Box 3117.1)
  - Sophian (photographs) (Box 3117.2)
  - Sophian (posters and negatives) (Box 3117.17)
  - Sophian (Box 3117.5, Box 3117.6, Box 3117.7, Box 3117.8, Box 3117.9, Box 3117.10, Box 3117.11, Box 3117.12, Box 3117.13, Box 3117.14, Box 3117.15, Box 3117.16, Box 3117.18, Box 3117.19, Box 3117.20)
  - Spectator (Box 3115)
  - Spectator
  - Tatler (Box 3118)
  - Tatler (Box 3118.1)
  - Tatler
  - Yearbooks
  - Yearbooks (photographs) (Box 3121)